♪♪
(alarm beeping,
Jane gasps)
(Sarah)
Okay, got your stuff.
Clothes, toothbrush.
You slept here?
Yeah.
Okay, look.
I know I shouldn't
have brought Dad
into your home
without asking.
But I know if I asked,
you would've said no.
Which is why you
shouldn't have done it.
You could have at least,
you know, shaken his hand
or said hi.
I won't talk
about this here.
Well, when do you wanna
talk about it, Kurt?
Taylor is alive,
Dad is innocent.
Her being back does
not change the fact
that someone
kidnapped her.
So, then talk me
through your version.
What, he got off
his shift, he abducted
the five-year-old
girl next door,
and then sold her on
the black market and came home
in time for the evening news?
I mean, what?
Someone knows what
happened that night.
It's not you
and it's not me.
So you still really
think he did it?
Or have you just been
mad at him so long,
you don't know
how to stop?
I want him gone by
the time I get home.
Okay, well, you don't
need to worry about it
'cause he's already
at a hotel.
He's just here
for some treatments.
He's still trying
to beat it?
No, Kurt.
They're just trying
to slow it down.
I gotta get
back to work.
Thanks for the clothes.
(sports game playing on TV)
(knocking on door)
What am I about to say?
"Three days are up.
Where's your cash?"
I'm working on it.
Oh, no, come on.
Don't make me
be this guy,
walking in here,
you know, talking about
breaking legs
or worse.
Ow!
Ah, ah!
Do you know what
I do for a living?
Yeah, I do.
And what's the FBI's stance
on agents with illegal
gambling debts?
What, you're gonna tell on me?
You're my bookie.
I'm saying, you don't pay,
it's out of my hands.
My bosses do what they do
to protect their reputation.
You wanna let go
of my arm now?!
Oww!
(panting)
That's a bad play, Tash.
One more day,
I'll have your money.
You better,
'cause the next time,
the conversation
ends different.
(door closes)
A breakthrough?
It was a dream.
(Borden)
Your first dream,
which you considered
significant enough
to mention to me.
A sex dream.
So what does it mean?
Well, that depends
on who you ask.
Most people believe that
dreams are the brain's way
of processing how we
feel about things.
So, who do you
think he was,
this dream man?
Um, something tells me
you have a theory.
What, you think
it's Weller?
You said that,
not me.
(Mayfair)
I hear you had
Jane over for dinner.
Yeah, it was
my sister's idea.
How worried
do I have to be
about your objectivity
on this case?
You don't.
It was a family dinner.
I mean, my nephew
was there, it was...
there was nothing
inappropriate.
No.
No, I ju-- no, I--
That guy had a tattoo
of a tree on his arm,
and Weller
doesn't have that.
Dreams aren't literal,
they're impressionistic.
Your body is covered
in tattoos,
symbols you
don't understand.
Now, you described it
as a tree with deep roots.
Maybe you're searching
for stability, strength.
Those are certainly
qualities
that Agent Weller
seems to project.
I'm speaking generally.
Normally your judgment
is beyond reproach.
But with her?
Look, we all know this
is an unusual situation.
Which is why
I need to know
that you're rock solid
out there,
that you're seeing
things clearly.
I am.
I'm saying you're not.
Your relationship
with Agent Weller
is... complicated.
He's your colleague,
your protector,
your childhood friend.
Yeah, and now he's in
my dreams. He's everywhere.
I think we need to
consider you stepping down
as lead agent
on this case.
It's not necessary.
(Borden)
Maybe you need to establish
clearer boundaries.
How do I do that?
To start...
try keeping your
interactions with him
limited to
a professional context.
At least for now.
Right.
(locker shutting)
Mornin'.
Hey.
Your holster's in
the wrong position again.
Right, sorry.
There's just so much new
stuff for me to remember.
We've already
talked about this.
If we're in a firefight
and your gun's
in the wrong position,
that mistake could cost
someone their life.
I said I was sorry, okay?
I don't need an apology.
I just need you
to make that adjustment.
Falcon is two minutes out.
Switch to alternate route
Bravo-three.
(tires screeching)
(man)
Everybody down!
No! No!
Oh, oh, God!
Uhh!
The target was Saudi Prince
Fawwaz al Aziz.
He was in town
on a peace summit.
There's been a lot of chatter
about Saudi extremist groups
targeting the Royal family.
Secret Service routes
are classified.
They tend to
change the day of.
So how did these guys pull off
an attack this coordinated?
Because they had this.
One of the shooters
had a mobile app
that I'd never heard of
called TRAKZER.
It hacks into the GPS signals
from "Blue Force trackers"
on government vehicles and
maps their exact location.
Where'd they get this
and who else has it?
The transactions
are untraceable.
Probably done through
the Dark Web.
The Dark Web?
That doesn't sound good,
what is that?
95% of the Internet
isn't indexed
on commercial
search engines.
Yeah, the Dark Web
is like the Wild West.
Everything from weapons
to sex trafficking.
Yeah, and now,
assassinations.
Shouldn't we hand this over
to the Cyber Division?
Here, take a look
at the app's logo.
That owl's on my leg.
(Patterson)
Exactly.
So, whoever did this
to her knew about the app?
How many government vehicles
have these trackers?
All of them.
So every single
government agent
is now a potential target...
including us.
♪♪
in their unmarked car
by converging vehicles.
No one could figure out how
they coordinated the attacks.
They tracked
their patrol car.
More variations
on the same theme.
An ambush in a prison bus
convoy in Houston.
A federal witness
killed in D.C.
TRAKZER's gone national.
And the death toll's rising.
We gotta shut
this down fast.
Whoever wrote this app
made it look like
it's being hosted
by a government network.
Any attack that
we launch on it
would be hitting
our own systems.
Great.
So, shutting
this thing down
is like trying to find
a needle in a haystack.
No, it's like finding a piece
of hay in a haystack,
like a very
specific piece of hay
in the haystack.
Yeah.
Okay, well,
you totally get it.
Yeah.
Actually...
Wait a second,
I have an idea.
I checked the signature elements
in TRAKZER's source code
against our malware database.
I understood
the word "database."
Each programmer has a--
a distinctive coding style.
Like a fingerprint.
Exactly.
And fingerprints
from the software
match a recent
Hackathon winner.
Sponsored contests for
recruiting programmers.
Now, check out
the winner's username.
The Horned Owl.
That's our guy.
How do we find him?
I traced the P.O. Box
on his Hackathon entry form,
and it routes to an
apartment in Bed-Stuy.
Hay in a haystack.
Nice work.
Let's go get him.
(rock music playing
in distance)
No.
Reade, you're up.
Bust it.
(rock music blasting)
♪ Hey! Hey! Hey! ♪
FBI, show me your hands!
What's going--
Put your hands up!
What's going on?!
(Zapata)
Clear.
Turn the music off!
Turn it off!
(music stops)
Does anyone else
live here?
No, what is this?
That owl on the door...
that symbol,
is that you?
Yes.
You created TRAKZER?
Of course I did.
I created it for you.
I work for the U.S. government.
Ana Montes,
I'm Special Agent Zapata.
I'm not saying anything
unless it's my direct
point of contact.
Right... and that's...
Leonard Gail,
National Security Agency,
Information Systems
and Security Division.
And you do what
for the NSA, exactly?
Nothing you're cleared
to hear about.
Just have your boss
call Leonard Gail.
(speaking in Spanish)
Okay, so because my
last name is Montes,
you think
I speak Spanish?
I read your
Social Services file.
I know your parents
passed away,
and I am sorry
to hear that.
I get it.
My dad left
when I was five,
my mom was an alcoholic.
My brothers and I practically
raised each other.
(speaking in Spanish)
(chuckles)
(door opens and closes)
I hate teenage girls.
I'm gonna go get Weller.
Stay here.
What part of
"I'm not talking"
don't you people
understand?
What is this?
Where did you
get that?
I don't know.
It's on your leg
and you don't know?
Look, it's hard
to explain.
Please, can you just
tell me what it is?
She got a healthy imagination,
I'll give her that.
She could be
telling the truth.
I mean, federal agencies
hire hackers
to red-team them all the time,
it's how they find
the vulnerabilities
in their security systems.
She's 17.
Yeah, for a hacker,
she's in her prime.
I just spoke to my
NSA counterpart.
Leonard Gail
doesn't exist.
I knew she was lying.
Or, Leonard Gail does exist
and the NSA is lying,
like they've lied
to everyone about
everything ever.
Well, what does
your gut tell you?
Are we dealing with
a government agent
or a kid who's read
too many spy novels?
What if it's neither?
So, the owl is just
a personal thing?
It didn't come
from anywhere else?
Because we can't find it
referenced anywhere.
Did you design it?
No.
Well, do you
know who did?
My brother.
I saw in your file that
he was killed last year.
I'm sorry.
Do you live
alone now?
Me, too.
It's hard,
all that quiet.
I'm used to it.
I'm not.
My brother was older.
He mostly worked nights.
I was alone a lot.
So he drew that
owl above my bed,
so I wouldn't be scared.
That thing was supposed
to make you less scared?
(laughs)
Well, owls are nocturnal,
so he said it would
keep away the bad guys.
Did it work?
No.
Your brother sounds
pretty special.
I don't wanna talk
about this anymore.
Did you talk
to Leonard Gail?
What did he say?
We talked to the NSA.
He doesn't exist.
You're saying
I'm a liar?
No, I'm saying that
you were probably conned
by someone who claims
they work for the NSA.
(scoffs)
Of course the NSA
told you that Leonard
doesn't exist.
His job is like 100 levels
above your clearance.
Look at these.
They're recent crimes targeted
at government vehicles...
which were located
by your software.
No.
(Weller)
Yes.
No, my-- my software
isn't real.
It was just
a proof of concept.
It wasn't for people
to actually use.
Well, "people" are using it.
Did you ever meet
Leonard Gail in person?
No.
You didn't give your
software to the good guys.
You gave it to someone
very dangerous.
And every second
it's out there,
more lives are at risk.
People are dying, Ana.
Oh, my God.
Ana, we need you to get
this software offline.
I can't.
(Weller)
You have to.
No, you don't understand.
There's no way for me
to shut it down.
What do you mean
you can't shut it down?
Look, TRAKZER isn't
on my servers.
It's on Shawn's.
Who is Shawn?
Shawn Palmer.
He approached me online
a few months ago.
He said that he was
hiring freelancers
for his cyber
security firm.
So, I did a few projects
for him and then he said
he wanted to meet
me in person,
that he had this
big opportunity.
All right,
so he was the guy
that said he worked
for the NSA.
Yes, and other,
less-reputable businesses.
Look, he said the NSA
wanted to test
their GPS security,
and he told them that
if I couldn't break in,
that nobody could.
He promised that they'd
hook me up with a job after
if I pulled it off.
So, I wrote the code
and then he sent it
to his contact.
(Jane)
Leonard Gail.
You didn't check
into Shawn's story?
I thought he was
looking out for me.
I guess I just...
Wanted it to be true.
(Weller)
Listen to me.
The longer this
is out there,
the more people are
gonna get hurt or die.
We need your help
to get to Shawn Palmer.
What do you need?
Palmer's security firm
is a front.
Outstanding warrants for
unauthorized computer access,
wire fraud,
identity theft.
And, ladies,
he is single.
And invisible--
Cyber Division couldn't even
find a photo, let alone
an address.
I could find his username
with DARPA's
Deep Web crawler,
or track his Bitcoin usage
in the Blockchain.
Or Ana could just
tell us where he lives.
She's been to his house.
Oh, sure, I mean, it's
a little analog, but--
All right, let's go
get Mr. Palmer and bring
him in for a chat.
Wait, wait, wait, guys,
it's not that easy.
Shawn's place is like this
crazy, fortified smart-home.
He keeps his
servers there.
The guy literally
never leaves.
Fine, we break
down his door.
No, a guy like Palmer
has an eject button.
He sees law enforcement
coming, he's gonna take
the software open source.
Open source?
Meaning he'll put TRAKZER's
code online for free.
This thing could go
viral in hours.
Well, if we can't get in,
let's draw him out.
What, like pull his
fire alarm or something?
No.
The guy is careful, smart
enough to know a false alarm.
What if it wasn't
a false alarm?
Reade, Zapata.
Are you in position?
(Zapata)
Ready when you are.
(Weller)
Patterson, what's our ETA?
I need a few more minutes.
This guy has
a massive firewall.
Blocked ports,
encrypted traffic,
intrusion detection.
Here, why don't you
try accessing--
Don't touch
my keyboard!
Okay.
You are a hacker.
This computer is behind
the FBI firewall.
No way you're
touching this, kid.
Was just gonna suggest
entering through
the emergency cell backup
on his smart-home control--
Yes, and accessing his
cameras and the alarms.
I was just gonna do that,
if you would just...
let me type.
Maybe if you were
writing in Python
instead of Perl,
you'd move faster.
What's wrong with Perl?
Nothing...
if you're designing
a website in the late '90s.
Whatever.
I see you switching.
I was gonna
switch anyway.
You shouldn't have gone
in there with Ana.
Why not?
Because you shouldn't be
interrogating suspects.
I was talking to her.
And now, you're emotionally
invested in that girl.
So, what if I am?
She is a scared, lonely kid.
Who is the subject of
an investigation.
FBI agents are trained
to maintain their distance.
I'm not an FBI agent.
And yet, you want
to be treated like one.
You wanted a weapon,
so you got--
Which you agreed to,
because it was
too dangerous for me
to be in the field
without one.
What's changed
all of a sudden?
In this job you have
to remain objective.
Really?
Is that what
you've done with me?
Stayed objective?
I'm working on it.
(computers pinging)
(Patterson)
Okay, you guys
should have eyes.
Now, I can shut off Shawn's
alarm and security systems,
but the freeze is only gonna
last for about 90 seconds.
That's all we need.
Okay, Zapata,
you're up.
Look for a lever marked
"Primary Voltage Converter"
that controls the power
going into Shawn's place.
All right, how high
do you want it?
(chuckling)
As high as it goes.
I like your style.
(converter chirping)
Okay, I've already
electronically jammed his fuses,
and his wiring should
short out any second.
(electronic music playing)
♪♪
Whoa, what the hell?
(circuits exploding)
No, no, no, no, no.
Oh, my God,
this can't be happening.
(typing)
(fire igniting)
No, no, no, no,
no, no, no.
(Patterson)
911, what is your emergency?
Um, my place is on fire.
Send someone fast!
We have a truck in your area
and we'll be there right away.
And, sir?
Please evacuate your home
and get as far away
from the fire as possible.
That was kinda cool.
(typing)
Okay, get ready, guys.
He's coming out hot.
(Jane)
What is he doing?
Trying to be a hero.
(coughing)
Come on.
Get out.
Get out of there!
Oh, God.
Let's move.
We're going in.
(grunting)
Come on.
(coughing)
(Patterson)
This is all that comes up
when you try to use
Ana's software now.
TRAKZER is dead.
What about Shawn Palmer,
is he cooperating?
Yeah, the nice thing about
arresting scumbags,
they're not big on
honor among thieves.
He's rolling over on every
Dark Web player we know of
and some we don't.
What happens to Ana now?
Well, she thought
she was working for us
and she cooperated when she
found out that she wasn't.
So, as long as she stays out
of trouble during probation,
she's free to go.
This case felt different
than the others.
Yeah, none of us almost
got killed for a change.
But we've been dealing with
corruption so much lately,
I was starting to think
the tattoos were from an enemy.
Foreign spy agency,
something.
But this time they
exposed technologies
trying to harm
our agents,
like they were
looking out for us.
So, whoever did this to me
is trying to help?
Or want us
to think they are.
Hey.
What has got
you twisted?
That kid breaks the law,
profits from it,
and gets a slap
on the wrist.
She never made
any money off of it.
We're supposed to take
her word for it?
If she got
paid in Bitcoin,
we'd never be able
to trace it,
we'd never
know for sure.
Come on.
Palmer was the get.
Ana was in over her head.
She's a 17-year-old kid,
on her own,
just trying to use
her skills to survive.
Dirty money
is dirty money.
(Jane)
Shawn hurt a lot of people.
And he probably would
have hurt a lot more
if you didn't
help us catch him.
You should feel good.
I feel stupid.
He was just the first person
in a long time who...
Forget it.
(clears throat, sniffles)
Do you want a ride home?
I'm sure somebody
here could take--
I'll be fine.
Listen, if you--
if you want...
if you ever want somebody
to grab a coffee with...
I don't drink coffee.
Right.
I just mean, if you
ever wanna talk.
Or we could
catch a movie.
I can almost promise you
I won't have seen it.
Maybe.
Can I talk to you?
Was I not clear before?
That is not
how we do things.
Well, maybe you
do things wrong.
Ana didn't open up
until I showed her
a little compassion.
And her opening up
saved lives.
The case is finished.
And, what, you're
inviting her to a movie?
She is completely
alone in this world,
and she needs something in
her life other than her work.
Jane...
Jane, if you ever
wanna come and have
a drink with the team--
No, I...
It's a little
hard to relax
when everybody at the table
has been staring at photos
of your tattooed body
all day.
What about Sarah?
Your sister?
Her last name
is on my back.
Look, I appreciate everything
that you've done for me,
everything that
you're doing.
But I just...
I don't know, I...
I need room to breathe.
Hey.
Do you have a minute?
Sure.
Uh, it's about
Saul Guerrero.
His case number
is on Jane's body,
and I've been digging
through his file,
but it's pretty redacted.
Talk to Mayfair.
She'll get you
compartmentalized clearance.
Uh, that's the thing.
I did,
and she won't help.
This is a pretty
big lead.
Don't you think it's a little
weird not to follow it?
I wouldn't read
into it too much.
I just don't understand why
we're not following up on this.
Fine, I'll look
into it, all right?
If Mayfair says
there's nothing there,
there's probably
nothing there.
Okay.
(gasping)
What do you want from me?
Fix your ap.
The software's
too complicated, okay?
That took me weeks
to code.
We don't need
the whole thing.
Just find this truck.
You have an hour.
That's not enough time.
Can you find it
or not?
I can find it.
You're still at my place?
What have you been
doing there all day?
I cleaned.
What do you mean,
you cleaned?
You know, laundry, tidying.
There may have been
a Swiffer involved.
Did you touch
my board games?
Yes.
I alphabetized them.
Wait... they were
alphabetized,
by game designer!
Oh.
Um... well, I think
I can remember--
No, no, it-- it-- it's fine,
I'll just do it when I get home.
But the place does look
very nice, though.
(keyboard clacking)
(buzz buzz)
What's wrong?
Someone is trying to access
the system with my login.
I'm being hacked.
Through your FBI firewall?
Who-- who's good enough
to do that?
I think I know.
Palmer said
you were fast.
This is not fast.
I'm going as
quick as I can.
It sounds to me like
you articulated
your desire for space.
It didn't go very well.
Well, setting boundaries
is challenging.
Even in more conventional
relationships,
people struggle to balance
intimacy and autonomy.
You and Agent Weller
have an--
Unconventional
relationship, yeah.
You didn't tell Weller
what we talked about
this morning, did you?
Jane, our sessions
are confidential.
Whatever you share,
it stays here.
What makes you ask that?
Because he's
pushing me away.
And that upsets you?
Perhaps Agent Weller is feeling
the same need for boundaries.
(knocking on door)
Sorry to interrupt.
Patterson needs
to see us right now.
She's not picking
up her cell.
I think the hack
was an S.O.S.
How do you know
it was her?
The first half of the code
was written in Python
and then it
switches to Perl.
It's an inside joke.
It's her.
So, where is she?
Can we track her location?
Nope, her IP address is
routed through relay proxies.
That's the only way
she could've hacked
into our firewall.
God, what's happening to her?
That's what I'm
trying to find out.
Got it!
This is live on Ana's webcam.
Oh, God.
All right,
the guy with the gun.
Can you capture his face enough
to use recognition software?
(computer beeping)
Okay, Misha Volkov.
Enforcer of the Petrovich
Heroin Syndicate.
Russian drug runners.
They must know that
she built TRAKZER
and want to track
DEA movements.
Which means they
need her alive.
For now.
That's Ana's apartment.
Let's get Reade
and Zapata, we gotta move.
Clear.
(Weller)
Clear!
Clear.
We must have
just missed them.
Hey, can you get
on this computer,
find out what
she was tracking?
Yeah, I can try.
One more time.
(keyboard clacking)
Wait, the username.
Is that Ana trying to
leave us a code?
No, that's a VIN number.
She's showing us what
they're tracking.
And how to find her.
These guys are always
late for the transfers.
(knocking)
Finally.
(gunshot)
Uhh!
(whimpers)
(gunshot)
Agh!
(groaning)
(sobbing)
(gunshot)
(siren bloops)
That was Patterson.
The VIN belongs
to an unmarked Homeland Security
transport truck.
It's carrying weapons on
the way to get shipped aboard.
That's a massive arsenal.
We can't let that
fall into their hands.
Any word from
the drivers?
DHS lost contact.
♪♪
It's all right.
We're gonna find her.
I know you think
I'm too invested.
We're all invested now.
Let's get her safe.
(truck beeping)
(whistles)
(siren blaring)
(gunfire)
(Weller)
R.P.G.! Move!
(high-pitched ringing)
Do you see Ana?
No, no sign of her.
(grunts)
(man)
Get the girl!
(gunfire continues)
(muffled grunting)
There.
Cover me!
What?!
(gunfire)
Go.
Uhh!
(grunting)
Come on, come here.
You're okay.
(Reade groaning)
Gah!
(gun firing)
Aah!
(truck starting up)
He's getting away!
Whoa!
Aah!
Thank you.
Did the medic
clear you?
Yeah, yeah, just, uh...
(clears throat)
...a couple bruises.
Thanks for...
coming to get me.
You're welcome.
So, what's next?
They're going to,
uh, keep you
under protective custody
for a while, just to be safe.
It's not that bad.
You don't know what any of
your tattoos mean, do you?
(sighs)
We're working on it.
Figure out that
steganography yet?
What?
The black square
on your shoulder.
Steganography?
(Patterson)
Steganography, of course.
Can you fill
the rest of us in?
It's a-- a method
of concealing messages
in innocuous images.
It's used by spy services,
terrorists--
it dates back to
the Ancient Greeks.
So the black isn't
just covering
the Navy SEAL
tattoo underneath.
Oh, well, that's the thing,
it's not all black.
Some of it's off-black.
So, uh, if you
isolate those sections
and change their
values to white...
(gasps)
The mask isn't covering
the message.
The mask is the message.
It's a classic
puzzle trick.
The dead space
is always a clue.
Do you know
what it means yet?
I mean, it looks
like a turtle shell,
but that's not
very helpful.
I mean, maybe it's a--
a substitution cipher
using grid fragments,
but that could take days
to decode, or longer.
So, no?
Not yet.
But we're on it.
You're saying every
one of these tattoos
could have
a double meaning?
Or triple.
Or more.
We should go back
over every tattoo
that we've already
decoded.
I mean, the CDC symbol,
the drone pilot's name,
even my name on Jane's back.
Nothing's dead.
Any of them can
hold another clue.
(clears throat)
Thanks.
Do you want
a new lead agent?
What?
On your case.
Back in
the surveillance van,
you said...
I wasn't objective.
So I can step down.
Mayfair can assign you
a new lead agent.
I shouldn't have
said that.
I was upset.
You might be right.
Maybe there's too much
baggage between us.
Or maybe the baggage
is what makes you
the right guy
for the job.
Who else
is more invested?
Do you want me
to give you a lift home?
My security detail's
downstairs.
It's no big deal.
It is on my way home.
Better not.
Good night.
Hey, I was gonna catch
the end of the Knicks game
down at 1849,
you wanna come?
Mmm... next time.
You sure?
Never seen you
turn down 20-cent wings.
Yeah, I think I'm
just gonna crash.
You know, if something's up,
you can talk to me, right?
Do you need to talk?
Is that what
this is about?
Good night, Tasha.
Good night.
(locker closes)
Kurt...
I told you
I wanted him gone.
Son...
Just sit down
for one minute.
He needs to hear it
from the both of us.
Hear what?
You haven't told him
about Jane, have you?
Who's Jane?
What's going on?
Just sit down.
Please.
Where'd you find this
kind of stack in 12 hours?
Couch cushions.
Giants are laying
six on Sunday.
Which way you leaning?
Out.
I'm out, Randy.
Yeah, I heard
that song before.
Not from me.
I'll see you soon, Tash.
They still don't know
what happened to her,
or who took her,
or where she went
or how sh--
how she got back.
But they did
the DNA tests.
And it's definitely her.
Dad, Taylor's alive.
(sobbing)
She is.
♪♪
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Um... do you guys want
to go out somewhere?
Grab a beer, maybe?
Sorry, ma'am, we're not
permitted to take you
to an unsecured location.
Right, um, well, what about
coming in for a drink?
Just one.
Sorry, ma'am.
But we can have a bottle
sent up if you'd like.
No, that's, um...
thanks anyway.
♪♪
(man)
Greg, move your head.